[music]
>> The emphasis is placed more on the time
of sleep.
>> [music]
>> How long did you sleep?
That's fine. That's healthy. [music] So,
people care more about sleep quantity
rather than sleep timing in the West.
People don't know much about organs in
your body healing at different times of
the night. [music] In fact, if you tell
people that, they will be very
fascinated. I love seeing this clock
where the different organs heal at
different times of [music] the night
according to Chinese medicine. Sadly, a
lot of Westerners will think that that
is BS. We'll see. I think in years to
come, we'll find out that there's
probably great wisdom to this. Cuz I
don't know about you, but I definitely
feel different if I sleep, [music] let's
say, midnight to 8:00 a.m. as opposed to
10:00 p.m. to 6:00 a.m. 10:00 to 6:00 is
honestly the sweet spot. So, what about
you? When is your ideal time [music] to
sleep? And do you believe that different
organs heal at different times of the
night? Come and share with us.